surfcanyon.com 2014-02-19

# Surf Canyon Privacy Policy

  * 1\. Information Collection & Use
  * 2\. Information Sharing and Disclosure
  * 3\. Legal Disclaimer
  * 4\. Security
  * 5\. Contact Us

## 1\. Information Collection & Use

We are committed to protecting online user privacy. In order to ensure your privacy, information we collect is used only in the manner and for the purposes described below.

### 1.1 Registration

Surf Canyon Incorporated ("Surf Canyon") collects personal information when you use the Surf Canyon browser extension. Surf Canyon is the sole owner of the information collected by the Surf Canyon browser extension.

### 1.2 Children's Privacy Policy

Surf Canyon is not directed towards children 13 years of age or under and we do not knowingly collect any information from children 13 years of age or under through our web site.

### 1.3 Uses of Information

Surf Canyon uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the search results on selected search engines (currently Surf Canyon, Google, Yahoo!, Bing and Craigslist), to customize sponsored results (which are always clearly labeled as such) on Surf Canyon's search engine, to improve our services, and to provide anonymous, aggregate reporting for internal and external clients.

### 1.4 Profile

We store information that we collect through client-side cookies and server-side log files to create a "profile" of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information to information in the profile in order to provide tailored search results and sponsored results for you. We share your profile with other third parties in aggregate form only. We do NOT share your profile with any third parties.

### 1.5 Refinement Links

Specifically with respect to Refinement Links, as described in [http://blog.surfcanyon.com/2009/04/30/v204-further-refinements](http://blog.surfcanyon.com/2009/04/30/v204-further-refinements/), and as delivered by either Surf Canyon's browser extension or any of our partner browser extensions, the functionality requires that the user's query and IP address be sent to Surf Canyon's server. Neither the query nor the IP address are ever sent to any third party. Furthermore, this data is never stored and is immediately discarded once the server responds with the Refinement information.

## 2\. Information Sharing and Disclosure

### 2.1 Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners. This information does not identify individual users. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information. No registration, login or cookies are required to use any of our services.

### 2.2 Personally identifiable information:

We DO NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties.

## 3\. Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site

### 3.1 Log Files

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

With respect specifically to the Refinement Links, as discussed in section 2.2 above, all information is immediately discarded and no information is stored in any log files.

### 3.2 Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. Cookies enable us to target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but the ability for our service to provide accurate personalization for you may be limited.

### 3.3 Third Party Search Engines

When you execute a query on selected search engines (currently Google, Yahoo, Bing and Craigslist), the Surf Canyon browser extension may make additional network connections to the search engine and execute additional queries. The additional network connections may cause you to exceed a search engine's bandwidth limit more quickly. The additional search engine queries may affect the search engine's own personalization algorithms.

### 3.4 Third Party Advertisers

The ads that we deliver to users may be provided by our advertising partners. We share Web site usage information about users with reputable third parties for the purpose of targeting our advertisements on this site. The information that our advertising partners collect is not personally identifiable.

## 4\. Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us using our contact page.

### 4.1 Business Transitions

In the event Surf Canyon goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### 4.2 Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by means of a notice on our home page.

### 4.3 Exception to this Privacy Statement

Users who download a version of our application offered as part of the MyPersonality research project conducted by the University of Cambridge should refer to the [MyPersonality Privacy Policy](http://apps.facebook.com/mypersonality/disclaimer.php), which, for those specific users only, will take priority over this Privacy Policy in cases of conflict.

## 5\. Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us using our contact page.
